Jai Hind Friends, I am not a SEBI registered
advisor.  This video is
made for educational and informational purpose only.   Let's
talk about ICICI LBRD General Insurance
Company Limited.  ₹170 is the current
price trading.  A rise of 2% is being seen.
This company
gives a dividend of 0.7%.  Its fundamentals are good.  It has a
market cap of ₹88,000 crore.
Its PE is 32.  The book value is ₹330.
of ROC 25.  ROE of 19.  Earnings per share is
₹55 debt free and reserves are ₹16000
crore.  The promoter holding is
more than 51%.  The margin
is around 13%.  The company is generating good
net profit revenue
on quarterly basis and there is an increase in revenue on year on year basis also.
And after that, an
increase in net profit is also visible here.  There is
also an increase in the share on earnings.
Overall, this general insurance company is a
good company.  It is a good company.
In the times to come, we will see people growing in the same manner.  The
company has
announced its result date
and also the dividend.  Unaudited sorry
not unaudited but audited financial
results will be declared by the company for us
and along with that the company is also going to give us the final dividend.
Okay, right?  The meeting
date has been fixed by the company on April 15, 2026.
So the company is going to
give us dividend on 15th April.  To get updates on
bonus, split and dividend in the open market,
you
must join the channel membership by clicking on the join button.  Okay, right
?  So on the 15th the company will
declare the total dividend.  How much dividend does it
pay?  Yes, this company had
given an interim dividend of about ₹6.5 here.   of
₹6.50 in the previous quarter.  Right now this is the
final dividend or the inter yes, final
dividend.  So, the last
time the company gave a final dividend was in 2025 of ₹7 and
before that it was ₹6.  So, this time also we will
assume that like the last quarter,
we will see this company declaring a dividend of ₹7.  Okay, right?  The stock
chart is trading in the negative.
Recently, it has only declined.
Like it came in the market.  But if we look at the 3-year
chart, there is a good recovery.
After that, if a little sideways
triangle gives a breakout on the upper
side, then there will be a
possibility of a good rise in it.  Overall, if there
is a long term view then this stock can be held.
Shopping may take place.
Otherwise, if the view is of a smaller time frame
then there will be a problem for it.